[{"answer": " Im so glad that Monday is finally over", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " Me too.  Its always hard to start working again at the beginning of the week", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 12, "question": " Im so glad that Monday is finally over", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " How was your weekend?  Did you watch the Oscars", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Me too.  Its always hard to start working again at the beginning of the week", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " A little bit.  I was out until late, so I just caught the last few minutes.  I missed al", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 14, "question": " How was your weekend?  Did you watch the Oscars", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " The Departed.  The Queen, and Little Miss Sunshine were nominated too and ", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 18, "question": " A little bit.  I was out until late, so I just caught the last few minutes.  I missed al", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Yeah, I never saw The Departed.  I guess it must have been good.  Who won fo", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 22, "question": " The Departed.  The Queen, and Little Miss Sunshine were nominated too and ", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Forest Whitaker won for best actor and Helen Mirren won for best actress", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Yeah, I never saw The Departed.  I guess it must have been good.  Who won fo", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Oh, I like Helen Mirren.  Im glad she won.  I saw that Leonardo DiCaprio and Wil", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Forest Whitaker won for best actor and Helen Mirren won for best actress", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I love Leonardo DiCaprio.  Its hard to know who will win though", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Oh, I like Helen Mirren.  Im glad she won.  I saw that Leonardo DiCaprio and Wil", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " True.  I missed all of the red carpet action too.  That is my favorite part.  To b", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I love Leonardo DiCaprio.  Its hard to know who will win though", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " I know.  Me too.  This year was really good.  Let me see Oh yes.  Kat", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 43, "question": " True.  I missed all of the red carpet action too.  That is my favorite part.  To b", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " She always looks so good", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 48, "question": " I know.  Me too.  This year was really good.  Let me see Oh yes.  Kat", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " I know. She does. Reese Witherspoon looked really cute too.  She wore a short", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 49, "question": " She always looks so good", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Shes a great actress.  I like her a lot.  Did anyone look terrible on the red carpet", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 53, "question": " I know. She does. Reese Witherspoon looked really cute too.  She wore a short", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Oh my gosh.  Yes.  That was the most entertaining part.  You should have see", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Shes a great actress.  I like her a lot.  Did anyone look terrible on the red carpet", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Oh, I cant stand her", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Oh my gosh.  Yes.  That was the most entertaining part.  You should have see", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " I know.  She had this hideous dress on that was covered in feathers.  Plus, sh", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Oh, I cant stand her", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " What is up with her?  Doesnt she have a stylist", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 63, "question": " I know.  She had this hideous dress on that was covered in feathers.  Plus, sh", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Apparently not.  Brad Pitt looked good though", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 64, "question": " What is up with her?  Doesnt she have a stylist", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Of course.  He could never look bad.  Ha ha!  Did anyone else look bad", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Apparently not.  Brad Pitt looked good though", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Umm. Oh, I remember.  Leonardo DiCaprio didnt look too great", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Of course.  He could never look bad.  Ha ha!  Did anyone else look bad", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Leo?  He usually looks good", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Umm. Oh, I remember.  Leonardo DiCaprio didnt look too great", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " I know.  But last night it looked like he had just rolled out of bed.  He wore jean", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Leo?  He usually looks good", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " You mean everyone else was in black-tie attire and he wore jeans", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 72, "question": " I know.  But last night it looked like he had just rolled out of bed.  He wore jean", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Yes.  It was very strange.  It seemed like he didnt try at all to dress up and h", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 73, "question": " You mean everyone else was in black-tie attire and he wore jeans", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Strange", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Yes.  It was very strange.  It seemed like he didnt try at all to dress up and h", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Very", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Strange", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": "Wouldnt it be so cool to be able to walk down the red carpet like they do", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Very", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " It really would.  I would love to wear a beautiful gown and have my hair an", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Wouldnt it be so cool to be able to walk down the red carpet like they do", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " I know.  It would be so glamorous to be a movie star", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 87, "question": " It really would.  I would love to wear a beautiful gown and have my hair an", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " We should try to become movie stars.  You never know", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 88, "question": " I know.  It would be so glamorous to be a movie star", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " At our age?  I dont think so", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 89, "question": " We should try to become movie stars.  You never know", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Well, we can dream right", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 90, "question": " At our age?  I dont think so", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Yes, we can always dream", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Well, we can dream right", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Oh, this is my stop here.  Its been nice chatting with you", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Yes, we can always dream", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " You too", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Oh, this is my stop here.  Its been nice chatting with you", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Maybe next year we can have an Oscar party together", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 94, "question": " You too", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " That would be fun", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 95, "question": " Maybe next year we can have an Oscar party together", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " See you tomorrow", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 96, "question": " That would be fun", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "10-02", "aSentId": 97, "question": " See you tomorrow", "qSentId": 96}]
